

AHMED MOHAMED ABDEL-MONEEM

Front End Developer

E: ahmed.m.moneem@gmail.c

P: 01124269532

W: https://
ahmedmohamed26.github.io

L: https://www.linkedin.com/in/iahmedmohamed/

SKILLS

Angular +7

React Js

Rxjs

Redux

Node js (basics)

Flutter

Ionic 4

Type Script

Javascript

Cit

Gulp JS

SCSS

Bootstrap 4

Pug JS

HTML5

CSS3

PROFILE

Hi, I'm Ahmed Mohamed an energetic and enthusiastic front-end web developer eager to learn new technologies and build amazing stuff. I'm 28 years old, up I am enjoying building elegant and professional web pages in a modern way. I have developed my skills in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Angular, Reactjs, Nodejs, and other skills to help me fulfill high qualifications and Finished Military Service in Mar 2017.

EDUCATION

Good | Cairo Higher institutes, Mokattam

2011 - 2015

I'm a graduated system and information with Bachelor degree, Mokattam I've Learning In Cairo Higher institutes HTML, FrontPage, Economic, Marketing, Feasibility Study, Information Security, Network Security

EXPERIENCE

Front End Developer | AFAQY, Maadi

Dec 2021

- I made automatic systems to locate the car that you do some of the work assigned to it according to the business
- Unit testing with (Karma or jest)
- Create projects with angular +10 or Reactjs
- Work on projects related to e-commerce
- Responsibility For Restful APIs
- Performance And Usability Testing

Front End Developer | El-Dokan Software, Maadi

Feb 2021 - Nov 2021

- Work on projects related to e-commerce like (zahranstores | mobilaty | switchplus eg)
- Unit testing with (Karma or jest)
- Create projects with angular +7 or Reactjs (Next js)
- Responsibility For Restful APIs
- Performance And Usability Testing

Front End Developer | PROEMCS, Nasr City

May 2019 - Jan 2021

- Create projects with angular +7 or Reactjs
- Work on projects related to medical field
- Responsibility For Restful APIs
- Performance And Usability Testing
- Convert PSD || ProtoType To PugJS & SCSS

Front End Developer | Valux Apps, Nasr City

Jan 2018 - Apr 2019

- Create projects with angular +7 or Reactjs
- Responsibility For Restful APIs
- Performance And Usability Testing
- Convert PSD || ProtoType To PugJS & SCSS